Hey. Misionero.
- At last. eh?
- About time.
Let's see what's there.
Totally pure.
C'mon...
There was a fucking checkpoint
on every fucking corner!
The Leyras are up our arse.
They want to control the free market.
They want us to buy directly from them.
Shit! Then what the fuck are we doing?
This is my neighbourhood. arsehole.
I call the shots here.
You do as I say.
or I'm not paying you shit.
So move. arsehole. Get to work.
- All done?
- That's all of them.
Let's go.
Misionero. when are
you gonna lend me your sister?
Already sick of giving blowjobs?
Hi. Rosita.
What if I asked you out
to a party after your shift?
Stop bothering me. You better clear out.
Okay. prick head!
Stop playing Romeo and get to work.
Move it!
All good. Linda?
Come in. kid.
Look at him!
Look how skinny he is. a bag of bones.
My mum says maybe I got a tapeworm.
Take a sandwich.
We can't let this tapeworm starve.
Watch out. that's a lot of money
for a kid like you.
Whatever you need we're here.
He's seen us.
- What happened?
- We're in deep shit.
A bunch of assholes with guns.
One of them almost caught me.
but I got away.
Open up. They're still lurking around.
Come in.
Motherfuckers!
Lower your gun. arsehole.
On the ground!
Hands behind you!
From now on anyone who wants to sell
has to do it through the Firm.
They'll get a pay cheque
depending on the work they've done.
Those who don't obey.
will be executed.
Come on!
You're fucked. arsehole!
Resign yourself.
Accept your fucking destiny.
This will happen to those
who don't cooperate with the Firm.
To all those who dare to disobey.
Go and tell everyone
that we showed you mercy.
We sacrificed one soul
to save the rest.
Tell everyone
that we want peace and work for all.
Cut.
Upload it to the web.
I come to pay my respects.
Come in.
I brought this.
We made a collection in the squadron.
My "rabbit" wasn't perfect.
He was only a kid.
I don't even think
he was ready to be a father.
But one thing's for sure.
he wouldn't have double-crossed you.
not even with the drug squad.
He was one of us.
But now you need this.
You know that he was good.
My "rabbit" was good.
Why are they saying
all that stuff about him?
I don't know.
- The Army says what it has to say.
- And you?
He liked you.
He respected you.
Why do you betray him like this?
Why do you let them
talk about him this way?
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Don't go...
please.
Don't go.
Thank you...
for coming. for your help.
I know you're good.
I know it's not your fault.
Thank you so much.
Those beloved by God laugh!
Those beloved by God cry!
Those beloved by God are alive!
Hallelujah. my brethren!
Let us not waste this moment.
Let us focus on ourselves.
on our psyche.
Let us unite with God.
Sit down
and do not miss this communion
with Christ our Lord.
He is intense. Real.
He is the light.
I invite you my brethren
to dedicate your lives.
your souls. your bodies. your prayers.
to Christ our Lord.
We are the instruments of the Lord!
Never forget that.
- Can I help you. ma'am?
- Two bottles of cough syrup for adults.
My friend! Keep an eye on my stuff.
- Hey. man. how you doing?
- Cool.
This guy wants medication.
To stop spasms.
Let's go.
Baylo. sit here.
Thank you for seeing us. Commissioner.
Your ship was not authorized
to dock at this port.
Correct. our merchandise is blocked
by Customs for inspection.
But in our business
time is a decisive factor.
We need to ship it immediately.
And avoid a Customs inspection...
Thank you. Commissioner.
Problem? All our permits are
in order. that's why we're offloading.
- I want to look inside the container.
- Do you have a warrant for that?
Hey. brother.
Yes! He's a giant!
Put it all on him.
Destroy him!
- The container is in warehouse 15.
- Thanks.
You're welcome.
Hurry up. we don't have all night!
Hurry up with the second truck!
Hey! What the hell!
Let's go!